{
    "subject": "resource/Norma_Fox_Mazer",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Young-adult_fiction",
    "human_readable": "Norma Fox Mazer's genre is Young-adult fiction.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9730501770973206,
            "question": "What makes Norma Fox Mazer's work stand out in the young-adult fiction genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.910103440284729,
            "question": "Are Norma Fox Mazer's books considered classic young adult literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6792287826538086,
            "question": "What themes are often explored in Norma Fox Mazer's novels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.60976642370224,
            "question": "How has Norma Fox Mazer influenced the world of children's literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5727166533470154,
            "question": "What genre does Norma Fox Mazer write in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5375699400901794,
            "question": "Norma Fox Mazer's books are typically aimed at what age group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43147414922714233,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics found in Norma Fox Mazer's writing style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.360524445772171,
            "question": "Who might enjoy reading Norma Fox Mazer's books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2966296672821045,
            "question": "Give an example of a book written by Norma Fox Mazer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20030264556407928,
            "question": "Has Norma Fox Mazer won any awards for her writing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norma Fox Mazer's genre is Young-adult fiction.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7494_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a book written by Norma Fox Mazer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7494_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might enjoy reading Norma Fox Mazer's books?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7494_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common characteristics found in Norma Fox Mazer's writing style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7494_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7494_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7494_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7494_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7494_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7494_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7494_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7494_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7494_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7494_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7494_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Norma Fox Mazer's genre is young-adult fiction.\" The context mentions her as a young adult novelist and analyzes her work within the field of young adult literature."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}